easyinfo.in 2011-12-28

# Privacy

**General Policies**

 **Use of Links**

Throughout our Web pages, we provide links to other servers which may contain information of interest to our readers. The Easy Info takes no responsibility for, and exercises no control over, the organizations, views, or accuracy of the information contained on other servers.

Creating a text link from your Web site to the Easy Info Web site does not require permission. If you have a link you'd like us to consider adding to the Easy Info Web site, please send e-mail to [webmaster@easyinfo.co.in](mailto:webmaster@easyinfo.co.in) with the subject "Link request."

 **Using Text and Images**

If you would like to publish information that you find on the Easy Info Web site, please send your request to [webmaster@easyinfo.co.in](mailto:webmaster@easyinfo.co.in). Where text or images are posted on our site with the permission of the original copyright holder, a copyright statement appears at the bottom of the page.

Information about using the Easy Info logo and images is available in Media Resources. Easy Info Web banner ads and buttons, along with instructions for their use, also are available.

 **Accessibility**

This Web site is designed to be accessible to visitors with disabilities, and to comply with federal guidelines concerning accessibility. We welcome your comments. If you have suggestions on how to make the site more accessible, please contact us at [webmaster@easyinfo.co.in](mailto:webmaster@easyinfo.co.in).

 **Privacy Policy**

Easy Info has created this statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The Easy Info does not collect personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. This policy is your guide to how the Easy Info will handle information we learn about you from your visit to our Web site.

 **Reading or Downloading**

In order to help make our Web site more useful to visitors, we utilize web measurement technologies to collect information on the number of visitors to the different sections of our site. Specifically, we use persistent cookie technology to measure multiple session traffic to our domain, easyinfo.in and compile reports with Google Analytics and MediaMind. We do not collect any personally identifiable information and collect and store only the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet ; the date and time you access our site; the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked to our site, and select browser information including version number, Java and Flash support level, screen resolution and language.

Easy Info will only use this information internally to analyze current Web site usage and determine the most effective way to customize and deliver our online content. We will not disclose this information to others. For data protection, we set first-party cookies and send information only to the servers of our domain, ensuring that the information cannot be altered or retrieved by any service on another domain. Additionally, all persistent cookies are set to expire within one year, consistent with OMB guidelines.

By default, most browsers enable persistent cookies. If you wish to opt-out of our web measurement you may do so by disabling persistent cookies in your browser. General instructions on how to alter the settings of commonly used web browsers may be found at http://www.usa.gov/optout_instructions.shtml. Opting-out of our web measurement will still permit you to access all of our Web site content.

 **Online Application**

To request an application to the Easy Info, you may fill out our Preliminary Data Page and share your personally identifying information. This information will be used only to determine your interest in Easy Info programs and related Volunteer programs.

We may use your contact information to send further information about the Easy Info or to contact you when necessary. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the "Opt Out" section below.

 **Sending Us an E-mail**

You also may decide to send us personally identifying information, for example, in an electronic mail message containing a question or comment, or by filling out a Web form that provides us this information. We use personally identifying information from e-mail primarily to respond to your requests. We may forward your e-mail to other Easy Info employees who are better able to answer you questions. We may also use your e-mail to contact you in the future about Easy Info programs that may be of interest.

We want to be very clear: We will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. Except as might be required by law, we do not share any information we receive with any outside parties.

If you sign up for one of our e-mail lists, we'll only send you the kinds of information you've requested. We won't share your name or e-mail address with any outside parties.

 **Kids and Privacy**

For children who visit our site, special rules apply. We do not request personal information about children, such as first and last name or street address and city. When kids send e-mail to us, their online contact information (e-mail address) is not used to re-contact them and is not maintained in retrievable form.

 **Opt Out or Change Your Contact Information**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications. These same options may be used to change or modify information previously provided to us.

Questions About Our Policies

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at:
